okay so hello everybody thank you for
好，大家好，谢谢
joining this webinar and title
加入此网络研讨会和标题
consumer-driven contracts in your micro
微观中由消费者驱动的合同
service architecture before we go to the
服务架构，然后再去
main topic let me say a few words about
主要话题让我说几句话
myself so my name is marcin jiseok I'm
我自己，所以我叫marcin jiseok
working for this print cloud team and
在这个印刷云团队工作，
developer at pivotal I'm working mostly
关键的开发人员，我主要在工作
on the free project so sprinkles sleuth
在免费项目上，所以撒了侦探
the spiracle contract so the one that
零星的合约，所以那个
we're going to talk about today and the
我们今天要谈论的是
latest one spring cloud pipelines my
我的最新一期Spring Cloud Pipelines
twitter handle is at MJ shark and my
Twitter句柄在MJ鲨鱼和我的
blog is too much coding comm I'm pretty
博客太多编码通讯，我很漂亮
sure it's impossible for you to protect
确保您无法保护
my name so you can find my twitter
我的名字，所以你可以找到我的推特
handle at my blog site which is much
在我的博客网站上处理
easier to memorize ok so what's on the
更容易记住，所以这是怎么回事
agenda I think that's very simple so
议程，我认为这很简单，
basically there's going to be an
基本上会有一个
introduction then a demo in the summary
介绍，然后是摘要中的演示
then nothing complex okay so ladies and
那没什么好复杂的，女士们和
gentlemen may I have your attention
先生们，我能引起你的注意吗
please
请
since there is like in the in the in the
因为在
internet a quite a big commotion related
互联网引起了很大的骚动
to what contracts are what is
什么合同是什么
consumer-driven contracts and stuff like
消费者驱动的合同之类的东西
that so the first things I'm going to
所以我要做的第一件事
talk to you about is what we will not be
跟你说的是我们不会的
talking about so we're not going to talk
在谈论，所以我们不会谈论
about schemas with those ESB success
关于那些成功实现ESB的架构
deeds accessories and stuff like that
行动配件和类似的东西
it's not gonna happen so the idea of
它不会发生，所以
sprinkler contract is not to introduce
喷水合同不介绍
any unnecessary coupling or replicate on
任何不必要的耦合或复制
the state right we seen some things go
正确的州，我们看到了一些事情
wrong sprinkle contract is not like
错误撒合同不像
reinvention of the same thing and why
重塑同一件事，为什么
I'm going to show you that in a second
我将在一秒钟内向您展示
ok so so in order for us to be on the
好的，这样我们才能进入
same page we have to use the same
我们必须使用相同的页面
vocabulary so let's define some terms
词汇，所以让我们定义一些术语
that we will be using throughout the
我们将在整个过程中使用
whole session so a producer a producer
整个会议，所以制片人
is a service that exposes an API right
是公开API权利的服务
simple stuff then we have it
简单的东西，那么我们有它
humor consumer is a service that
幽默消费者是一项服务，
consumes the API of the producer so if
消耗生产者的API，因此如果
you are sending a request to another
您正在向另一个人发送请求
server then you are consuming that
服务器，那么你正在消耗
services API what is a contract a
服务API是什么合同
contract is an agreement between a
合同是
producer and a consumer on how the API
生产者和消费者如何使用API
will look like it's a recent statement
看起来像是最近的声明
typically some companies write those
通常一些公司写那些
down in documents like who you know word
像你认识的人这样的文档
or console and stages we don't we don't
或控制台和舞台，我们不，我们不
want to use that we need something that
想要使用我们需要的东西
can be inside code and that can help us
可以在代码内部，这可以帮助我们
bind those sides to the to this
将这些方面绑定到此
agreement now consumer driven contract
现在协议，消费者驱动的合同
is an approach where the consumer is
是消费者在
driving the changes of the API of the
推动API的更改
producer what does it mean it means that
生产者这是什么意思
since the consumer is the one that is
因为消费者是
using the API that's why it's called a
使用API​​的原因就是它被称为
consumer it knows best how do you
消费者最了解您
actually look like and how it's done in
看起来和如何完成
practice you're going to see during the
练习你会在
demo so whenever somebody tells you
演示，这样无论何时有人告诉你
about a new tool or a new approach
关于新工具或新方法
the first thing you should always ask is
您应该经常问的第一件事是
what problems are we trying to solve
我们要解决什么问题
because often somebody here is a new
因为这里经常有人是新来的
slogan you like tool and immediately
标语您喜欢的工具，并立即
somebody says let's use it in our
有人说让我们在我们中使用它
company but if you cannot answer the
公司，但如果您无法回答
problem like what kind of a problem will
像什么问题一样的问题
this tool solve you shouldn't be using
这个工具解决了你不应该使用
that so what problems are we trying to
那我们想解决什么问题
solve with sprinkle contract and
用洒水合同解决
consumer different contracts as such the
消费者这样的不同合同
first one is stub validity and
第一个是存根有效性，
reusability in the integration tests and
集成测试中的可重用性
now what our integration test so we're
现在我们的集成测试是什么
on the same page again so when I when I
再次在同一页面上，所以当我
use the phrase integration test it means
使用短语集成测试意味着
a test that is drunk they run during the
他们在测试期间喝醉的测试
build time so you're building your
建立时间，以便您建立自己的
application and some tests are let's say
我们说应用程序和一些测试
working on mocks and stubs and stuff
处理模拟，存根和东西
like that these are unit tests and
就像这些是单元测试
integration tests are those tests that
集成测试是那些
send real requests to fake HTTP servers
发送真实请求到伪造的HTTP服务器
or access in memory database so I'm
或访问内存数据库，所以我
talking about those
谈论那些
the latter the latter test the second
后者后者测试第二个
problem we're trying to solve is
我们要解决的问题是
creation of a nice nice API so we have a
创建一个不错的API，所以我们有一个
typical situation we have a consumer
我们有消费者的典型情况
that is sending a request to the
发送请求到
producer I guess
我想是制片人
typically this is how your production
通常这就是您的生产方式
looks like more or less maybe you have
看起来或多或少
more services so how would you write a
更多服务，那么您将如何写
test like for this particular scenario
对于这种特定情况进行测试
so the first approach could be exactly
所以第一种方法可能就是
the same thing so you run your consumer
同样的事情，所以你经营你的消费者
up you run the producer up and you
你使生产者运转起来，你
perform end to end test which is often
执行端到端测试，这通常是
fine but if you have Micro Services or
很好，但是如果您有Micro Services或
if the model is very hard to actually
如果模型很难实际执行
run if your for example have monolithic
例如，如果您运行的是单片
applications then basically you know you
应用程序，那么基本上你知道你
can have different sorts of problems
可能有各种各样的问题
like on the producer side how do I set
就像在制作人那边，我该如何设置
up the database do I need some special
数据库上我需要一些特殊的东西吗
tables in that database do I need more
该数据库中的表格我需要更多吗
services should I stop something like
服务我应该停止类似的事情
manually so there's a bunch of problems
手动，所以有很多问题
typical to end to end test so another
典型的端到端测试，所以另一个
thing that you can do is that the
你可以做的是
consumer is talking to a stub right why
消费者正在与存根聊天，为什么
would you want to do this because you
你想这样做是因为你
will have much faster feedback because
会有更快的反馈，因为
it's run during the build time right so
它在构建期间运行，所以
let's like check this example in more
让我们像检查更多这个例子
details let's say that the consumer
细节说，消费者
application is called pivotal calculator
应用程序称为关键计算器
service and what you can see here is
服务，您在这里可以看到的是
that consumer application right and it
消费者申请权及其
contains some JSON mappings of HTTP
包含HTTP的一些JSON映射
server stub so the examples you're going
服务器存根，因此您要使用的示例
to see in a second are using the wire
一秒钟内看到使用电线
mock which is a tool to stop a chain
模拟是阻止链条的工具
HTTP server so it's using some stub
HTTP服务器，因此正在使用一些存根
definitions from wire mock right so
电线模拟的正确定义
we're on the consumer side and the
我们在消费者方面，
consumer owns the stub definition
消费者拥有存根定义
this is very a critical eye as a
作为一个非常关键的眼睛
consumer I'm writing tests and I say in
消费者我正在写测试，我说
like I define how the producer should
就像我定义制作人应该如何
behave and what does it mean what what
表现，这意味着什么
is this stop let's check it out
是这站吗，让我们看看
this is an example of a stub definition
这是存根定义的示例
with the wire mark so you have a let's
带有电线标记，让您拥有
ignore the priority section it's
忽略它的优先级部分
completely relevant we have requests and
完全相关，我们有要求，
response right so like with mojito for
响应正确，就像与mojito一样
instance you say that given something
例如，你说给了一些东西
return some value so this is exactly the
返回一些值，所以这正是
same thing so if you're sending a
同样，如果您要发送
request with a method post to URL
请求与方法发布到URL
history then the response should be as
历史，则响应应为
state as 201 and content-type header
状态为201和内容类型标头
should be equal to application Jason
应该等于应用Jason
another example you're sending a HTTP
另一个示例，您正在发送HTTP
request with a method could URL would be
具有方法的请求可能是URL
history and a body should contain my
历史和身体应该包含我的
value like five plus five and then the
像五加五的值，然后
response will be having status 200 there
响应的状态为200
will be a JSON inside the body result 10
将是在正文结果内部的JSON 10
counts for e2 for example and header is
例如，计数为e2，标题为
content type application Jason last
内容类型应用程序Jason last
example you're sending a toast method to
例如，您要向其中发送吐司方法
URL history body should contain a value
网址历史记录正文应包含一个值
text value six plus six and then the
文字值六加六，然后
response should be 400 so like given
响应应该是400
given some condition like our request
给定一些条件，例如我们的要求
should look like then some response
应该看起来像这样一些回应
should be sent back so let's focus on
应该寄回去，让我们集中精力
this example I as a consumer have this
这个例子我作为消费者有这个
JSON file where I define how the
我定义的JSON文件
producer should behave and I have this
制片人应该表现出来，我有这个
URL history so how about I just change
网址历史记录，所以我如何更改
it from history the URL from history to
从历史记录到URL从历史记录到
some non-existent URL why not I can do
一些不存在的URL为什么我不能做
it because I own the stub so basically
因为我基本上拥有存根
it's it's kind of trolling but I can do
这是一种拖钓，但我可以
it so what happens now so I change the
所以现在发生了什么，所以我改变了
stub definition so I'm saying that the
存根定义，所以我说的是
producer will behave in a different
生产者的行为会有所不同
manner my test tool
我的测试工具
fail because I'm shooting a request and
失败，因为我正在拍摄请求，
a non-existent URL right so in my
一个不存在的URL，所以在我的
production code I was saying that I'm
我说的生产代码是
going to shoot at request flash history
将根据要求拍摄闪光记录
but now my stub is saying hey there is
但现在我的存根说嘿
no such girl I have some non existing
没有这样的女孩，我有些不存在
URL so I rewrite my code to work with
网址，因此我重写了要使用的代码
the newer URL I just changed the new URL
我刚刚更改了新的URL
now the unit and integration tests pass
现在单元测试和集成测试通过
because I fixed my implementation I
因为我固定了实现方式
think the production code and I think
认为生产代码，我认为
the tag and now since in the deployment
标签，现在开始部署
pipeline I went through the build phase
我经历了构建阶段的管道
I'm deploying the application to
我正在将应用程序部署到
intervene at an environment where a real
在真正的环境中进行干预
integration state played so we have a
整合状态发挥，所以我们有一个
couple of deployed applications and some
几个已部署的应用程序和一些
end-to-end tests will take place and
端到端测试将进行，
obviously I have nothing to worry right
显然我没什么好担心的
because my build is green I passed the
因为我的建筑是绿色的，所以我通过了
test unfortunately that's not the case
不幸的是，情况并非如此
because when like the moment those tests
因为当那些时刻
are run there was going to be a disaster
运行，那将是一场灾难
on this environment like hopefully some
在这种环境下希望
staging and not production so what
分期而不是生产怎么办
what's it go wrong let's check it out
怎么了，让我们检查一下
stubs that were used in the build phase
构建阶段中使用的存根
have nothing to do with the real API I
与真实的API无关
arbitrary change the URL to some
随意将URL更改为一些
non-existent your URL my desktop how is
您的网址不存在，我的桌面如何
it so we goes physical humor is all
所以我们身体幽默就全部了
owning the stubs I said today when I
拥有我今天说的存根
send this bizarre you like message to
发送这个奇怪的消息给
non-existent URL we have unicorns
不存在的网址，我们有独角兽
because the result is okay because this
因为结果还可以，因为
table says yeah sure
桌子说是的
your head the response will look like
你的头反应会像
this but in reality when I was sending
这但实际上当我发送
that request to the producer on the same
对生产者的相同要求
this during those end-to-end tests the
在那些端到端测试中
producer said what there is no such
制片人说没有
endpoint 404 so the problem that we're
端点404，所以我们遇到的问题
trying to solve the stub validity and
试图解决存根的有效性和
reusability the problem was that stubs
可重用性的问题是存根
reside with the consumer consumer
与消费者一起居住
controls the stubbing process so how can
控制存根过程，如何
we ensure that this stubs are valid
我们确保此存根有效
because the consumer
因为消费者
right as I presented any stupid thing
就在我提出任何愚蠢的事情时
it won't right so this is one thing like
这是不对的，所以这是一回事
solidity and reusability so in one of
坚固性和可重复使用性
the projects that I was working on one
我正在从事的项目
of the companies we had a son
有一个儿子的公司
architecture because we had a monolithic
建筑，因为我们有一个整体
app in the middle and plenty of
中间有很多应用
microservices talking to it so every
微服务与之对话
team had to do we do the same work so
团队必须做同样的工作
they were stopping the models and the
他们正在停止模型，
problem was that the moment they created
问题是他们创造的那一刻
those stubs who are completely outdated
那些完全过时的存根
because the model is has changed in the
因为模型在
meantime
与此同时
and of course the stubs were insured
当然，存根已经投保了
between between the things so everybody
之间的事物之间，所以每个人
did the same work so that was the first
做同样的工作，所以这是第一个
problem another one is nice API creation
问题另一个是好的API创建
so the consumer is called a consumer
所以消费者被称为消费者
because it's consuming the idea and it's
因为它正在消耗想法，并且
cold like this for a reason because it
之所以这样冷是因为
knows how the EPI should look like
知道EPI应该是什么样子
thus they should take part in the
因此他们应该参加
creation of the API of the producer
创建生产者的API
often I would say in the majority of
我通常会说
cases what happens if the producer team
如果制作人团队发生了什么情况
says more goodmorning this is my API if
说更好，这是我的API，如果
you don't like it don't use it and the
你不喜欢它，不要使用它
consumers say eh tell me this API is
消费者说eh告诉我这个API是
like impossible to use we can't work
就像无法使用，我们无法工作
with it can you please change it and
有了它，你可以改变它，
typically what the producer team says is
生产者团队通常说的是
um sorry but we have to ever have a
嗯，抱歉，我们必须有一个
tight schedule you can talk too much to
时间表紧张，你可以跟太多人说话
our product owner who will put it into
我们的产品所有者将把它放进去
our sprints and maybe in half a year
我们的冲刺，也许是半年
we're going to fix it so that's not the
我们将修复它，而不是
way to go because everybody is unhappy
因为每个人都不开心而走的路
so the producers API change should be
因此，生产者API更改应为
driven by consumer because the consumers
由消费者驱动，因为消费者
are using the API so this is something
正在使用API​​，所以这是
that can happen if there is no
如果没有，那会发生
cooperation right the unit test asked
合作权单元测试问
but all together it doesn't fit right
但总的来说不合适
the consumer and the producer didn't
消费者和生产者没有
meet somewhere another example is
在另一个地方遇到另一个例子是
something like this so we thought that
这样的事情，所以我们认为
the fields should be ABC but entire they
字段应该是ABC，但整个字段
are des so yeah we have a problem
是的，是的，我们有问题
so we have to fix this problem somehow
所以我们必须以某种方式解决这个问题
so the potential answer to this problem
所以这个问题的潜在答案
is actually sprinkle contract so the
实际上是撒合同，所以
best way to show it is to code something
证明它的最好方法是编写代码
so what are we going to code actually so
所以我们实际上要编码什么
the consumer will be a an application
消费者将是一个应用程序
that receives beer requests somebody
收到啤酒的人
comes to the bar and says I want a beer
来到酒吧，说我要啤酒
so the consumer app will receive that
因此消费者应用会收到
request and it will have to ask another
请求，它将不得不问另一个
service about whether the client is
服务有关客户是否
eligible to get the deer so the consumer
有资格获得鹿，所以消费者
will send a request to the producer that
将向生产者发送一个请求
will say you know I have to check if the
会说你知道我必须检查
client is old enough to get the deer
客户年龄大到可以得到鹿
because the like to put things simple
因为喜欢把事情简单化
let's say that the age will be the
假设年龄将是
parameter that will define whether the
定义是否
person can give the bureau's so the
人可以给局的，所以
feature is that if the user is too young
特点是如果用户太年轻
the beer will not be sold and otherwise
啤酒将不出售，否则
the the beer will be granted for
啤酒将被授予
simplicity sake let's say that if
简单起见，如果
somebody is 20 or over uh he's going to
某人年满20岁或以上
get the beer if he's below 20 there's no
如果他不满20岁，就去喝啤酒
chance for getting a beer let's do it
喝啤酒的机会吧
like this because it's simpler to write
之所以这样，是因为它更容易编写
a regular expression so let's keep with
正则表达式，让我们继续
that yeah so how does it look like
是的，那看起来怎么样
somebody comes to the bar and says I'm
有人来到酒吧说我
20 to give me here so the consumer apps
20给我在这里，让消费者应用
has asked a can he get the beer and the
问了一个他可以拿啤酒和
answer is yes so the consumer says there
答案是肯定的，所以消费者说
you go and second feature you have the
你去，第二个功能，你有
consumer in the producer and somebody
生产者和某人中的消费者
comes to the bar and says I'm 17 give me
来到酒吧，说我17岁给我
a beer so the consumer asks the producer
啤酒，所以消费者问生产者
can he give the beer and the answer is
他可以给啤酒吗，答案是
no so we say get lost so typical stuff
不，所以我们说迷路那么典型的东西
that happens in the bar now important
现在在酒吧发生的事情很重要
thing because I've been giving this talk
事情，因为我一直在讲这个
a lot of times and I think this is the
很多时候，我认为这是
best way to differentiate between the
区分的最佳方法
consumer and the producer so whenever
消费者和生产者，所以无论何时
you see a black terminal
你看到一个黑色的终端
or a black IBE that is the consumer side
或黑色的IBE（即用户端）
I'll be also repeating that that we are
我还将重复说，我们是
on the consumer side whenever you see a
在消费者方面，只要您看到
white terminal or a white IDE it means
白色终端或白色IDE，表示
that we are on the producer side okay so
我们在生产者方面好吗
time for the demo let's go to the code
演示的时间，让我们看一下代码
so this is our consumer application
这是我们的消费者应用程序
since we don't have that much time
因为我们没有那么多时间
I have already some Clutton of the codes
我已经有了一些Clutton的代码
already I have almost no production
我已经几乎没有生产
codes I'm going to show you that in a
代码我将向您展示
second so consumer-driven contracts is
其次，消费者驱动的合同是
actually like TVD on the architecture 11
实际上就像TVD上的架构11
what does it mean like when you're doing
这是什么意思
TDD you start with the test and then
TDD，您先进行测试，然后
things have evolved so it's exactly the
事情发展了，所以正是
same way here with sprinkle culture but
这里也有撒文化
the idea is that the API will evil so
这个想法是API会邪恶，所以
what we're doing is that we're starting
我们正在做的是开始
with a test we have two features to
通过测试，我们有两个功能
write the first one is should give me a
写第一个是应该给我一个
beer when I'm old it off and the second
啤酒，当我老了，第二次
this should reject the beer went up to
这应该拒绝啤酒上升到
you so I'm going to copy some code here
你，所以我要在这里复制一些代码
so I don't make any mistakes
所以我不会犯任何错误
we're going to use mock MVC to UM do the
我们将使用模拟MVC来进行UM
testing let me do some static imports so
测试让我做一些静态导入，所以
there you go okay so um the test is
那里你还好，所以这个测试是
sending a post method in a post HTTP
在发布HTTP中发送发布方法
request to the beer endpoint with an
向啤酒端点请求
application JSON and the rivers that
应用程序JSON和
we're sending is person person has a
我们发送的是某人，某人有一个
name and an age so in this case if I
名字和年龄，在这种情况下，如果我
want to get the beer I wish I was 22 I'm
想喝啤酒，我希望我22岁
not but let's say that I am then the
不是，但可以说我当时是
status will be okay and the response
状况会很好，而且回应
will be there you go this is our feature
会在那里你走，这是我们的功能
and the second one a
第二个
is very similar but I am 17 and then
非常相似，但我17岁，然后
what should happen is that I receive a
应该发生的是，我收到了
get lost message right get lost so two
迷路的消息正确的迷路所以两个
features you're over 20 you get the beer
您超过20岁的人会喝啤酒
you're less than two any you don't you
你不到两个，你不是吗
don't get live here how does the
不要在这里住
controller look like like I told you
控制器看起来就像我告诉你的
I've created some skeleton of the code
我已经创建了一些代码框架
there's actually nothing here so
实际上这里什么都没有
basically we have a post method beer
基本上我们有一种后期方法啤酒
endpoint application JSON and a person
端点应用程序JSON和一个人
coming in so at this moment I should ask
进来所以这时我应该问
another I should send the request to the
另一个我应该发送请求到
producer to say a like can you check if
制片人说一个喜欢你可以检查
the person is eligible to get the beer
该人有资格获得啤酒
but actually the other site hasn't
但实际上另一个站点没有
written a single line of code if I
如果我写了一行代码
wanted them to create some like fake API
希望他们创建一些伪造的API
or something it would take it would take
或将需要的东西
some time so I want to experiment I
一段时间，我想尝试一下
don't even know if we either I'm going
甚至不知道我们是否要去
to pick is good so so how can we do that
选择是好的，所以我们该怎么做
and here it comes
来了
sprinkled contract so sorry the black
洒了合同，所以对不起黑人
screen we're on the consumer side tins
屏幕我们在消费者方面
during the demos I don't I really don't
在演示中，我不，我真的不
want to use the internet so we're going
想使用互联网，所以我们要
to do a permanent version of cloning a
做一个永久的克隆版本
project so right now as a consumer I'm
我现在作为消费者的项目
going to clone the producers code boom
将克隆生产者代码热潮
like ice cloned it so as a consumer I
像冰一样克隆它，作为一个消费者我
have cloned the producers code now let
现在已经克隆了生产者代码
me check out the proper branch and right
我检查出正确的分支，对吧
now I will open that project yeah so
现在我要打开那个项目
we're on the consumer side I'm opening
我们在消费者方面，我正在开放
the producer local project let's wait
生产者本地项目让我们等待
for the yes for everything to import so
对于所有导入的是
right now you can see that there is no
现在你可以看到没有
code here there's only producer
这里的代码只有生产者
application no controllers nothing like
应用程序没有控制器没什么像
that so why did I do it I did it
那我为什么要做
because I'm interested in the pump like
因为我对泵感兴趣
in the properly set up project so in the
在正确设置的项目中
poem I have a very important piece of
我有一首很重要的诗
code which is this one so sprinkles
这就是这样的代码
contract maven plugin why do I have it
合约Maven插件为什么我有它
you're going to see in a second what I'm
你将在一秒钟内看到我是什么
interested in is this part so under
对这部分感兴趣
source test resources I have contract
我有合同的源测试资源
what are those contract we define that a
我们定义的那些合同是什么
contract is an agreement between the
合同是
consumer and the producer on how the API
消费者和生产者如何使用API
should look like and here I'm going to
应该看起来像，在这里我要
use this word for the last time like
最后一次使用这个词
first and last time but it's not a
第一次也是最后一次，但这不是
schema it's related more to a feature
模式，它与功能更多相关
that we want to test but it's also a
我们要测试，但这也是
look like you shouldn't have that many
看起来你应该没有那么多
contract as many features you have
签约您拥有的许多功能
because the idea of contract testing is
因为合同测试的想法是
to test the semantics and not to replace
测试语义而不是取代
like do the feature twice once in the
就像在功能中一次执行两次
code and once in the in the contract so
代码，然后在合同中一次
here I've created two tool contracts in
在这里我创建了两个工具合同
sprint all contract you do it with using
冲刺您使用的所有合同
groovy DSL so let's check out how the
普通的DSL，所以让我们看看
contract looks like here we have the
合同看起来像这里
first case so should grant a beer if if
第一种情况，如果
I'm old enough we have a factory method
我够大了，我们有工厂方法
from contract class and if any one of
合同类别以及以下任何一项
you is scared of groovy because it's a
你害怕时髦，因为这是一个
dynamic language I have to very much
动态语言，我必须非常
disagree because it can be dynamic and
之所以不同意是因为它可能是动态的，
personally I love groovy when it's
我个人喜欢groovy
statically typed so the DSL is
静态类型的，所以DSL是
statically typed everything you're going
静态键入您要进行的所有操作
to see here our methods are things that
在这里看到我们的方法是
are statically typed so the compiler
是静态类型的，因此编译器
will help us at every point of us
将在我们的每一个方面为我们提供帮助
writing the code so let's say that I
编写代码，所以说我
want to play around the dapi of the
想要玩的dapi
producer so let's say that the method
生产者，所以说方法
that I would like to that they use would
我希望他们使用
be both armed the URL let's assume that
双方都准备好URL，我们假设
it can be checked maybe
可以检查一下
went on and I will send some body in
继续，我会送一些身体
groovy you can use the map notation to
时髦，您可以使用地图符号
define a body using spiritual contract
用精神契约来定义一个身体
basically Jason is a map right I mean it
基本上杰森是一张地图，对不起
can have a list of maps and map of lives
可以有一张地图和生活地图的清单
it can have everything basically any
它基本上可以拥有任何东西
sort of combination you can imagine
你可以想象的那种组合
that's why it's very hard to work with
这就是为什么很难与之合作
Jason when you need to parse it but what
杰森，当你需要解析它，但是
kind of a body I would like to send so
我想寄出这样的尸体
let's say that I would like to have a
假设我想有一个
JSON where there's going to be a few
JSON将会有一些
code name where the name will be
代号名称
marching and the age will be 22 this is
游行，年龄将是22岁
how I defined in a very nice like
我如何定义一个非常好的
readable manner how the info Jason
可读方式如何信息杰森
should look like and now time for the
应该看起来像，现在是时候了
headers so let me create a header header
标头，让我创建一个标头
key would be a content type and the
关键是内容类型，
value would be application JSON so here
值将是应用程序JSON，所以这里
I define certain requests that I would
我定义了一些我会要求的要求
like to be matched when taking into
喜欢被匹配时
consideration the should grant the beer
考虑应该给啤酒
is old enough scenario hi for the
已经足够老了
response since I don't endure any
回应，因为我不忍受任何
mistakes I'm going to copy it from here
错误，我要从这里复制
and I'm going to explain you what I did
我将向您解释我做了什么
so the response is I assume in this case
所以在这种情况下，我认为是
to have status 200 this is another way
拥有状态200这是另一种方式
of defining a body inspector contract so
定义身体检查员合同的方式
in groovy you can do a multi-line string
在groovy中，您可以做多行字符串
by providing those free characters so
通过提供那些免费字符
here I just defined what kind of a JSON
在这里，我只是定义了哪种JSON
I would expect if the person is eligible
我希望这个人有资格
to get the beer and the in the response
得到啤酒和回应
I want the content type to be equal to
我希望内容类型等于
application JSON there's some magical
应用程序JSON有一些神奇之处
magic going on around here don't mind it
魔术在这里不介意
at the moment what we expect is that the
目前，我们期望的是
response will have the application JSON
响应将具有应用程序JSON
content type right so here we define a
内容类型正确，所以在这里我们定义一个
very
非常
contract that for the request with
与之签订合同
method post and URL check if the body
方法发布和URL检查主体
contains the name marching in aged 22
包含22岁时行军的名字
and it's actually a JSON we expect the
它实际上是一个JSON，我们期望
response to have status 200 and body
回复状态为200和身体
having a JSON with a field status of
具有字段状态为的JSON
value okay and the header would be
值还可以，标题为
application JSON so for the second
应用程序JSON，因此第二个
scenario what I'm doing is that pH is
我正在做的是pH值是
it's 17 then the status should be notes
现在是17，状态应为备注
ok so this is the part in which I as a
好的，所以这就是我作为
consumer I'm playing around with the
消费者，我正在和
contract of the producer but why do I
生产者的合同，但是我为什么
even do that what's the point so let's
即使这样做也很重要，所以让我们
go back to our terminal I as a consumer
回到我们作为消费者的终端
I am in the cloned producers code what
我在克隆的生产者代码中是什么
I'm going to do right now is I'm going
我现在要去做
to clean install and skip tests of
清理安装并跳过以下测试
course you shouldn't be doing that with
当然你不应该这样
your like real production code right now
您现在喜欢真正的生产代码
we're playing around with the API that's
我们正在使用的API
why I'm doing and why is it so you're
为什么我在做什么，为什么会这样，所以你在
going to see in a second if we scroll up
如果我们向上滚动，将在一秒钟内看到
you will see spring cloud contract maven
您将看到Spring Cloud Contract Maven
plug-in in action so what happens is
插件在起作用，所以会发生什么
that print out contract maven plugin is
打印出合同的Maven插件是
analyzing the contracts that you have
分析您拥有的合同
defined and will convert them into the
定义并将其转换为
wire log stub mappings so if we go back
连线日志存根映射，所以如果我们返回
to the 2d code you'll see a target
到二维代码，您将看到一个目标
coming like here and in the mapping
像这里和映射中一样来
section you will see a wire mock stub I
部分，您将看到一个电线模拟存根I
have already shown you a an example of a
已经给你展示了一个例子
wire mock stubs during the presentation
在演示过程中连接模拟存根
phase so here you can see that the DSL
阶段，在这里您可以看到DSL
was changed into the wire mock JSON file
已更改为Wire模拟JSON文件
so here you can see that if somebody
所以在这里你可以看到如果有人
shows the you request to the URL check
显示您请求的URL检查
with a method post and content type
带有方法发布和内容类型
equals application JSON and here you can
等于应用程序JSON，在这里您可以
see that we're using JSON path to
看到我们正在使用JSON路径
analyze the JSON so the name has to be
分析JSON，因此名称必须为
marching and h22 if that's the case then
行军和h22如果是这样，那么
the response should be 200
响应应该是200
body should be stated okay and
身体应该没问题，
compensate application JSON so the first
补偿应用程序JSON，因此第一个
thing that the sprinkled contract maven
洒了合同的专家
plug-in Gradle as well does is it
插件Gradle也是吗
converts the DSL into the into this stub
将DSL转换成此存根
another thing that it does is that it
它所做的另一件事是
installs those stubs into your local
将这些存根安装到本地
maven repository so right now as a
Maven存储库现在作为一个
consumer I plainly replayed around with
我清楚地与之互动的消费者
the API of the producer and I installed
生产者的API，我安装了
it stubs into my mate and local why did
它存根到我的伴侣和本地为什么
I do this right now let's go back to the
我现在就这样做，让我们回到
consumers code so we're back this is our
消费者代码，所以我们回来了，这是我们的
test let's see if it passes obviously it
测试让我们看看它是否通过了
will not pass because we didn't write a
不会通过，因为我们没有写
single line of the like production code
单行之类的生产代码
boom of course it's not working so let's
繁荣当然是行不通的，所以让我们
write some code over here I have it here
在这里写一些代码我在这里
so I don't make any mistakes hopefully I
所以我希望不会犯任何错误
don't okay so let's do some import okay
不好吧，让我们做一些导入吧
so I'm sending a request using risk
所以我使用风险发送请求
template with a post method to the 30 to
带有post方法的模板到30
the 20 euro a URI local sauce 8090 with
20欧元的URI本地酱8090
a URL check application JSON and I'm
一个URL检查应用程序JSON，我是
sending a person there right and then
派人到那里然后
I'm checking the status as we had in our
我正在检查状态，就像我们在
acceptance criteria so there you go will
接受标准，所以你去
be sent back to the user once the status
状态一旦发送回给用户
is okay so the user can get the beer and
可以，这样用户就可以喝啤酒了
get lost will be presented if not let's
如果不让我们迷路的话
see if the tests pass obviously they
看看测试是否通过了
will not and we will have a very nasty
不会，我们会非常讨厌
exception which is IO exception and it
IO异常和它
makes sense because I sent a real
有道理，因为我发送了一个真实的
request to to a real URL but I didn't
请求到真实网址，但我没有
start any server right I mean you saw
启动任何服务器对，我的意思是你看到了
everything I was doing
我所做的一切
I just added some let's implementation
我刚刚添加了一些实现
but I didn't start any server so here
但是我没有启动任何服务器，所以在这里
comes rental contract on the consumer
与消费者签订租赁合同
side sprinkler contract contains a
侧喷头合同包含
module called table runner as you can
可以叫桌旗的模块
imagine stub runner run stops that's why
想象存根赛跑者跑停，这就是为什么
the name is quite good so I'm telling
这个名字很好，我告诉
stub runner to work offline what does it
存根赛跑者离线工作是什么
mean it means stub runner please find
这意味着存根转轮请找到
the stubs of my collaborators in my
我的合作者的存根
local maven repo that's why I installed
这就是我安装本地Maven存储库的原因
for the producers stubs like locally
对于本地的生产者存根
because right now I want to play around
因为现在我想玩
with the API of the producer so the
与生产者的API，因此
stubs are installed in my mail in local
存根安装在本地的我的邮件中
and here I'm saying the stops that I
我在这里说的是
would like you mr. Staub runners the
想要你先生。 Staub跑步者
download are those that have group ID
下载的是具有组ID的文件
comb example artifact ID the pure API
梳齿示例工件ID的纯API
producer with the latest version with
制作人提供最新版本
the classifier stubs and please register
分类器存根，请注册
them at port 89 if we go back to the
他们回到89号港口
terminal
终奌站
you will see that when I was installing
您将在安装时看到
the producer stubs you can see calm
生产者存根，你可以看到平静
example beer API producer
啤酒API生产商示例
0:01 snapshot and stubs are here the
0:01快照和存根在这里
classifier is stopped so theoretically
从理论上讲，分类器已停止
what I would expect is that when I run
我期望的是当我跑步时
it stub runner will download the stops
存根赛跑者将下载停靠点
from my Mason mavin logo will start a
从我的Mason mavin徽标开始
HTTP server stub and seeded with the
HTTP服务器存根，并以
stubs of the producer so if I didn't do
生产者的存根，所以如果我不做的话
anything wrong
哪里不对了
the test should pass and they did so
测试应该通过，他们这样做了
what happened why did they tasks if we
发生了什么事，他们为什么要任务，如果我们
check out the console here what happens
在这里查看控制台会发生什么
is that table runner has resolved the
是桌手解决了
version to the calm example Bureau API
版本到平静示例局API
producer jar with classifier stubs in
带有分类器存根的生产者罐
versions usually one snapshot it
版本通常是一张快照
and parked the contents of that jar and
然后把那个罐子里的东西停下来
fed the wire mock stub mcguire mock
喂电线模拟存根mcguire模拟
server with the stubs and started this
服务器与存根，并开始了
wire mop server at port 80 90 if you
如果您在端口80 90处安装有线拖把服务器
don't believe me we can go to beer
不相信我，我们可以去喝啤酒
controller I will put a breakpoint over
控制器，我将放置一个断点
here and let's run the first case so
在这里，让我们运行第一种情况
should grant a beer when I'm old enough
我足够大的时候应该喝啤酒
we're running the test the breakpoint is
我们正在测试断点是
here and here you can see that in the
在这里和这里，您可以在
response in the body we hit status okay
我们的身体反应良好
and the header is application JSON so
头是应用程序JSON，所以
indeed it's working okay so this was
确实工作正常，所以这是
magic of Stricker contract but the idea
Stricker合约的魔力，但是这个主意
behind the whole flow is to play around
整个流程的背后是玩转
with the API so suddenly I say it's kind
使用API​​，所以突然我说这是一种
of stupid that I whatever I receive on
愚蠢的我无论收到什么
my side and sending to the producer
我的身边，并发送给生产者
right same object but the producer
正确的对象但生产者
shouldn't care about the name I mean the
不应该在乎我的意思是
only criteria should be the age so let's
唯一的标准应该是年龄，所以让我们
say that I'm going to play around with
说我要去玩
the API I don't like how it currently
我目前不喜欢的API
looks like and the awesome thing is that
看起来很棒，
I haven't written a single line of the
我还没有写过一行
implementation on the producer side
生产者方面的实施
where right I just play around with the
我只是在哪里玩
contract I'm going to send a request
合同我要发送请求
where I'm going to pass only the
我将只通过
person's age that the only thing that
人的年龄唯一
has changed so let us run the tests
已经改变了，让我们运行测试
again let's see
再来看看
going to happen boom the test failed why
即将发生的繁荣测试失败了为什么
is it song that's because I don't match
这是因为我不匹配的歌吗
the contract so wire mob tells me that
合同，所以电线暴徒告诉我
the closest match is the one that has
最接近的匹配是
both fields age and the name whereas I'm
两个字段都年龄和名称，而我是
sending an age field only so I said hey
只发送年龄字段，所以我说嘿
okay fair enough that my bad I forgotten
好吧公平，我的坏事我忘记了
about this so basically it should like
关于这一点，基本上它应该喜欢
ring it better it should ring a bell
最好打个铃
this kind of situation where for example
这种情况例如
in the API you've made a typo so if you
在API中，您输入错误，所以如果您
make a typo your tests will no pass
输入错误，测试将不及格
because the closest match will be the
因为最接近的匹配是
one it doesn't have the typo so we go
一没有错字，所以我们去
back to the to the contract and we say
回到合同，我们说
hey I mean the name should be there
嘿，我的意思是名字应该在那里
right let's let's remove the nei what
好的，让我们删除nei什么
we're doing right now is that we will
我们现在正在做的是
install the stubs locally from the
从本地安装存根
producers the running clean install and
生产者正在运行的全新安装和
we're skipping test
我们正在跳过测试
well why we're skipping test you're
那么为什么我们跳过测试你
going to see that in a second when we go
我们去的时候一秒钟就会看到
to the producer side so here again the
到生产者方面，所以这里再次
stubs were created if we check them out
如果我们签出存根，就会创建存根
here in target no longer do we have the
在目标这里不再有
name field so if we go back to the
名称字段，所以如果我们返回到
consumer and we rerun the tests I would
消费者，我们会重新运行测试
expect those tests to pass because the
希望这些测试通过，因为
name field is no longer required and
名称字段不再是必需的，并且
that's the case so another thing that
是这样，另一件事是
I'm doing is that if I go back to my
我正在做的是，如果我回到我的
tests and I say actually I would like
测试，我说我实际上想
this test to pass if I'm 50 and 10 as
如果我50岁和10岁，则该测试通过
well of course here I'm kind of
当然，在这里我有点
duplicating the functionality but the
复制功能，但
idea is to show you that if instead of
想法是告诉你，如果不是
an age you would have a time stamp or a
您将拥有时间戳或年龄的年龄
database ID you would have two for
您将拥有两个数据库ID
example they're coming back to this time
例如他们回到这个时候
stamp for example you would have to set
例如，您必须设置图章
like fix a clock in your test to always
像将时钟固定在测试中
set the same value of of time in your in
在您的时间设置相同的时间值
your example so we will
你的例子，所以我们会
this to happen right the contracts would
这是正确的合同
be very rigid and let's say we would
非常僵化，假设我们会
introduce some coupling in the form that
引入一些耦合形式
you would have to have very precisely
你将不得不非常精确地
created requests that can be like
创建的请求可能像
difficult to achieve so what we can do
很难实现，所以我们能做些什么
and right now if I run the test it
现在如果我运行测试
should fail because we would expect the
应该失败，因为我们期望
values of age to be 22 and 17 and that's
年龄分别是22岁和17岁
the case so what we can do is use
这样的话，我们可以做的就是使用
dynamic values that come with sprinkler
洒水器附带的动态值
contract so to do this what I will do is
签约，所以要做的是
call a method called value and say that
调用一个名为value的方法并说
a consumer would like to have a regular
消费者想要定期
expression here so if I'm old enough it
在这里表达，如果我够大的话
means that the value of H would be the
表示H的值为
first digit would be from 2 to 9 and the
第一位数字是2到9，而
last one is 0 tonight that's why I
今晚最后一个是0，这就是为什么我
wanted to have this like if you're over
想像这样结束
20 then you're eligible for the beer
20，那么您就有资格喝啤酒
because it's easier to write a regular
因为写一个普通的书更容易
expression in case of if you're not old
如果你不老的话
enough the regular expression will look
正则表达式看起来足够
like this right so the request should be
像这样的权利，因此请求应该是
matched when the age is smaller than 19
年龄小于19岁时匹配
or equal to 19 so what we're going to do
或等于19，所以我们要做的是
right now is that we will run the
现在，我们将运行
installation of stubs again with
再次安装存根
skipping test on the producer side on
在生产者方面跳过测试
the pinnacle sorry on the consumer side
消费者对不起的顶峰
but in the clone producer code so the
但是在克隆生产者代码中
same thing as we have been doing for the
与我们为之所做的相同的事情
last couple of examples and right now if
最后几个例子，如果现在
I run it and I didn't do anything wrong
我运行它，但没有做错任何事
the test should pass because the regular
测试应该通过，因为常规
expressions will be matched so they do
表达式将被匹配，因此它们可以
awesome so right now as a consumer I say
我现在说的很棒，作为消费者
ok I planed a rap length around with the
好吧，我计划与
API I'm really happy with what we
API我对我们的工作感到非常满意
achieved this is the contract that I'm
实现了这是我的合同
satisfied with at this moment I am
此时此刻我很满意
filing a PR a pull request to the
向PR提出PR请求
producer so right now we are going to
制片人，所以现在我们要
the producer side we're here white
生产者方面，我们在这里白色
screen
屏幕
producer and now we're going to go to
制片人，现在我们要去
the white IDE there we are
我们那里有白色的IDE
so we are on the producer side and we
所以我们在生产者方面，我们
have accepted the pull request I mean we
已经接受了拉取请求，我是说我们
have taken it over so we didn't yet
已经接管了，所以我们还没有
merge it but we see a TR and we're going
合并它，但是我们看到一个TR，我们要
to play around with it right I have to
玩弄它，我必须
speed things up I have created a very
加快速度，我创造了一个非常
simple producer controller where I have
我有的简单的生产者控制器
person to check person to check there's
人员检查人员检查
only H that's it's nothing more and the
只是H，仅此而已
response will be having status equal to
响应的状态将等于
either ok or not OK
可以还是不可以
that's it so what we're going to do
就是这样，我们要做的是
right now is we're going to call clean
现在是我们要打扫干净
install I haven't written a single test
安装我还没有写过一个测试
whatsoever let's run it and see what
让我们运行它，看看有什么
happens
发生
why did I mean what what happened I
我为什么要说我发生了什么
haven't written a single test so why do
还没写过一个测试，为什么
I have to failing test so sorry
我必须考试不及格，很抱歉
so what happens is that sprinkle
所以发生的是洒
contract maven plugin except for for the
合同Maven插件，除了
fact that it's converting contracts into
它正在将合同转换为
stubs it's also converting contracts
存根它也在转换合同
into tests so here you can see that for
进行测试，因此在这里您可以看到
those two examples I should grant the
那两个例子我应该给予
burek old enough and should reject the
burek年纪大了，应该拒绝
dirac too young it's creating two tests
狄拉克（Dirac）太年轻，正在创建两个测试
these tests are completely
这些测试是完全
auto-generated what do those tests do so
自动生成这些测试的功能
if here we say that if I'm old enough
如果在这里我们说如果我够大的话
and I'm sending a method post you're of
我正在发送一个方法发布给你
like a week request with a method post
就像一个方法请求的一周请求
to a URL check with certain body that
到带有特定正文的URL检查
match is a regular expression then we
match是一个正则表达式，那么我们
expect status 200 and the status ok in
期望状态为200，状态为ok
response so actually we are creating a
因此，实际上我们正在创建一个
request with header content type
标头内容类型的请求
application JSON with age matching the
与年龄匹配的应用程序JSON
regular expression expression and we're
正则表达式，我们
sending the post methods of a post
发送帖子的发布方法
method to the check URL and then we
检查网址的方法，然后我们
expect status code to be 200 and content
期望状态码为200，内容为
type to match application JSON
键入以匹配应用程序JSON
and the cool thing is that we also check
很酷的是，我们还检查了
the body to point do we do that what why
身体指向我们这样做是为什么
because if you're lying
因为如果你在说谎
in your contract that things work like
在您的合同中，事情就像
this then we want like this test to
然后我们要像这个测试
break so my implementation is not
中断，所以我的实现不是
prepared whatsoever to to do to let's
准备要做什么让我们
say be compliant with these with this
说与此合规
contract that's why this auto-generated
合同，这就是为什么自动生成
test fails so I need what I need to do
测试失败，所以我需要做的事情
is to write some implementation here so
是在这里写一些实现
if person to check has an H greater or
如果要检查的人的H大于或
equal to 20 then I'm returning a new
等于20然后我要返回一个新的
response with berchik state is equal to
berchik状态的响应等于
okay I'm doing things it's rapidly so
好吧，我正在做的事情很快
I'm going to run the test the
我要进行测试
auto-generated tests again okay one has
自动生成的测试又可以了
passed so which one has passed the one
通过了，哪一个通过了
that is sending a real request to my
向我发送真正的请求
controller and checking if state is it
控制器并检查其状态
okay so let's run the write the second
好吧，让我们运行第二个
thing here we turn new response with
在这里，我们有了新的回应
beer check status equal to not okay
啤酒检查状态等于不正常
running this and both tests pass so
运行这个，两个测试都通过了
right now as a computer as a producer I
现在当电脑，当制作人
know that my implementation is matching
知道我的实现是匹配的
what's written in the contract I can
我可以在合同上写什么
prove it also by running the build so
通过运行构建来证明这一点
I'm running the build the auto generated
我正在运行自动生成的构建
test has passed and I have installed the
测试已通过，我已经安装了
stubs locally what is critical is to say
本地存根至关重要的是说
is that these are the same contract that
是这些是相同的合同
the consumer was using to write his own
消费者习惯于自己写
tests so we have one source of truth
测试，所以我们有一个真理来源
that is shared between both both party
双方共享
so right now what I would do in the in
所以现在我会在
the real word is that once I merge the
真正的意思是，一旦我合并了
pr SEI tool like builds the producer
pr SEI工具，例如，建立生产者
code and uploads the jars with the
代码并使用
father on the app and the stops to some
在应用程序上的父亲和一些停止
artifact 3 Nexus or something like that
神器3 Nexus或类似的东西
right
对
then let's now switch the consumer side
那么现在让我们切换消费者
then inside my and inside my where is
然后在我的内在和我的内在哪里
this contrary consumer test I would
这种相反的消费者测试我会
switch the work of lying to false and
将说谎的工作改为假，
provide a URL to my Nexus like your my
提供与我的Nexus一样的网址给我
Nexus or artifactory comm / leaves
Nexus或人工通讯/离开
release local whatever that way whenever
随时以任何方式释放本地
I build my app like build my run the
我建立应用程式就像建立我的执行
tests
测试
the latest stubs like the world the ones
世界各地的最新存根
that you have provided here will be
您在此处提供的将是
downloaded and my tests will be run
下载并运行我的测试
against this right but since I don't
反对这项权利，但由于我不
have an artifact tree here let's go back
这里有一个神器树让我们回去
to the working of offline so the last
到离线工作，最后
thing to show you is that if I go back
告诉你的是，如果我回去
to the producer code sorry then let's
到生产者代码，抱歉，让我们
say that for some reason I've decided to
说，出于某种原因，我决定
do a breaking change which I shouldn't
做一个我不应该做的重大改变
but I am because I don't know why I'm
但我是因为我不知道为什么
doing a breaking change and changing the
做一个重大的改变并改变
URL from check to beer check if I go
从支票到啤酒的网址，如果我去
back to my terminal clear I'm running
回到我的终端，我正在跑步
the maven build the auto-generated test
Maven构建自动生成的测试
should fail why is it so because there
应该失败为什么会这样，因为那里
is no such endpoint having the beer
没有喝啤酒的终点
check endpoint so I get 404 so if I if I
检查端点，所以我得到404，所以如果我
go back to the code and I fix the
回到代码，我修复了
situation like I fix the braking change
像我修理刹车的情况
I mean I I've been breaking change to
我是说我一直在努力改变
the production code if I go back to
生产代码，如果我回到
contract verifier here I can see the
合同验证者在这里我可以看到
their new URL so if I run those tests
他们的新网址，所以如果我运行这些测试
they should pass ok I go back to the
他们应该通过，我回到
terminal
终奌站
I run the maven build again the test
我再次运行Maven构建
should
应该
and I have installed the latest stops
我已经安装了最新的站点
local so right now if I go back to the
所以现在如果我回到本地
consumer code if I run those tests again
消费者代码，如果我再次运行那些测试
what should happen is that those tests
应该发生的是那些测试
will break so imagine the situation in
会破裂，所以想象一下情况
reality so the for the producer by some
现实，所以对于一些生产者
mistake or deliberately deliberately has
错误或故意
uploaded the contracts that are breaking
上传了违约合同
the backwards compatibility your tests
向后兼容性测试
will immediately break because the
将立即中断，因为
closest match this time is a different
这次最接近的比赛是不同的
URL so the one that was broken so in
URL，因此被破坏的那个
order for me to fix it I would have to
为了让我修复它，我将不得不
change there the implementation okay so
改变那里的实现好吧
concludes the demo let's go back to the
演示结束，让我们回到
presentation let's do some sort of a
演示文稿，让我们做一些
summary so what you could see is that we
摘要，所以您可以看到的是，我们
had that consumer phase one so the
拥有该消费者第一阶段，因此
consumer has some offline work done in
消费者已完成一些离线工作
which it's playing with the API like TDD
它正在使用像TDD这样的API进行播放
on architecture level it's playing with
在架构层面上
the AP on until it's happy the moment
AP直到开心为止
the contract is agreed upon can be the
合同约定可以是
moment where the producer is writing its
制片人写的那一刻
part so these things can go in parallel
部分，以便这些事情可以并行进行
so the moment the contracts are agreed
所以合同一经达成
both parties can work in parallel so
双方可以并行工作，所以
producer is implementing the feature and
生产者正在实施该功能，并且
then the consumer is switching to online
然后消费者转为在线
mode so let's look at the images so we
模式，让我们看一下图像，
have an example like where the consumers
有一个例子，如消费者
to the right or to the left we have a
在右边或左边，我们有一个
producer that owns this only the
拥有这只的生产者
contract right so the consumer clones
合同权利，因此消费者可以克隆
the producer code and works with the
生产者代码并与
local club there is a survey interaction
当地俱乐部有一个调查互动
going on between the consumer and the
在消费者和消费者之间
clones producer to play around with the
克隆制作人来玩
contract once the consumer is happy the
消费者满意后立即签约
it files the pr's of the producer with a
它将生产者的公关文件与
proposal of a new contract over or a
新合同的提议
change or something like that
变化之类的
so it's all about TDD so you write a
所以这都是关于TDD的，所以你写一个
test for the feature as a consumer you
以消费者身份测试该功能
clone the Perl code locally to change
在本地克隆Perl代码以进行更改
the API and remember you install the
API，并记住您安装了
stubs locally right so you clone the
本地存根，以便您克隆
producers code you install the stubs
安装存根的生产者代码
locally then you turn the stub Runner to
然后在本地将存根转轮
work in the offline mode because you
在离线模式下工作，因为您
don't want to download stops from Nexus
不想从Nexus下载停靠站
or are the battery you have to provide
还是您必须提供的电池
the group ID and artifact ID and
组ID和工件ID以及
versions stuff like that of the producer
像生产者一样的版本
if you go to sprinkle contract
如果你去撒合同
documentation you will see different
您会看到不同的文档
approaches to versioning please check it
版本控制方法，请检查
out and you do read bring every factor
出来，你确实会阅读所有因素
until you're happy with the API
直到您对API满意为止
once the API is acceptable and the test
一旦API被接受并进行测试
stops you're filing the pr2 the producer
停止您向生产者提交pr2
now the producer takes over the pr
现在生产者接管了公关
writes the missing implementation and
写缺少的实现，并
once the TR has been merged the CI tool
一旦TR合并了CI工具
will upload the stubs and the father jar
将上传存根和父亲罐
to Nexus or artifactory so we take over
Nexus或人工制品，因此我们接管了
the PR we write the missing
公关我们写失踪者
implementation and since we are using
实施，因为我们正在使用
spring cloud contract maven plugin there
那里的Spring Cloud Contract Maven插件
will be some auto-generated tests
将是一些自动生成的测试
created for us right that they have we
为我们创造了他们拥有我们的权利
have to make them pass we merge the TR
必须让他们通过我们合并TR
and that way we deploy the CI tool will
这样我们部署CI工具
deploy the application and the stops the
部署应用程序并停止
next Authority Factory then the consumer
下一个授权工厂然后是消费者
switches to online mode and then
切换到在线模式，然后
download the stubs of other
下载其他的存根
collaborators during the build site so
在构建站点期间的合作者
you have much faster feedback just like
您有更快的反馈，就像
I shown you you have to provide like
我告诉你你必须提供
works offline to to false by default
离线工作默认为false
it's false so you can remove that to the
这是错误的，因此您可以将其删除
line of course you have to provide the
当然，您必须提供
URL of the place where you store your
您存储您的位置的网址
artifacts like Nexus or at the factory
Nexus等产品或工厂
and you will have the test broken
这样你的测试就会失败
immediately once there is any breaking
一旦有任何破裂
change and here we go to a problem let's
改变，这里我们要解决一个问题
emerge is quite like often is that one
出现就像是经常出现的那样
does not simply clone somebody else
不只是克隆别人
people there are projects there are
人们那里有项目
situations where for security reasons
出于安全原因的情况
you cannot clone the producer code so
您无法克隆生产者代码，因此
what can you do them the only thing that
你能为他们做的唯一的事
changes is that the contracts no longer
变化是合同不再
they with the producer but they are in a
他们与生产者，但他们在一个
separate repo it's a normal maven
单独的仓库是一个普通的专家
project from which you will produce a
您将从中产生一个项目
job so the consumer clones repo and
工作，以便消费者克隆回购和
plays around with this locally and once
在本地玩一次
it's happy with the API people has a
人们对API感到满意
very strictly defined structure you can
您可以非常严格地定义结构
override it of course but there's some
当然要覆盖它，但是有一些
convention that allows you to do things
允许您做事的约定
very fast please check all the dogs I
非常快，请检查所有的狗我
don't want to like give you too much
不想给你太多
detail here because I'm just showing you
详细信息在这里，因为我只是向您展示
an overview and once the consumer is
概述，一旦消费者
happy with the PR it will be with the
对公关很满意
contracts APR is done through that repo
合同年利率是通过该回购完成的
over there and then the producer let's
在那边，然后制作人让我们
say takes over the PR so close the repo
说接管公关，所以关闭回购
locally right the missing implementation
对丢失的实现进行本地处理
and then once the PR gets merged then
然后公关合并后
during the CI the producer is reusing
在配置项期间，生产者正在重用
the contracts from this repo that has
来自此回购的合同具有
all the common contracts together and
所有共同合同
again jar with the stubs and the fuzz
再次用存根和绒毛震撼
jar is uploaded to next Authority
罐子上传到下一个授权
factory so the only thing that changes
工厂，所以唯一改变的地方
is the place where it used or contract
是它使用或签约的地方
so this is exactly the case when you're
所以当你
in for example for due to security
例如由于安全
reasons so what's important to remember
原因，重要的是要记住
here is that the repo with contract is
这是合同的回购是
also built by your CI so it produces a
也由您的CI构建，因此它会产生一个
jar with contract definitions then the
带有合同定义的罐子，然后
producer downloads that the jar you can
生产者下载您可以使用的罐子
configure that in spring contract maven
在 Spring 合同中配置Maven
plugin and finds its own contract
插件并找到自己的合同
definition either very convention or you
定义很传统或你
can override it the convention is that
可以覆盖它，约定是
there's a folder with the contract for
有一个合同的文件夹
the producer lay in the folder that is a
生产者躺在一个文件夹中
group ID artifact ID separated by
组ID工件ID分隔为
flashes the producer
闪烁制作人
creates tests and stuffs from those
从那些创建测试和东西
contracts so again we are verifying
合同，所以我们再次验证
whether the contracts are valid against
合同是否有效
the producer so nothing like changes in
生产者，所以没有什么变化
this regard the only thing that changes
这方面唯一改变的地方
is the place where the contract lay and
是合同订立的地方，
then the producer deploy the fat jar and
然后生产者部署胖罐，
jar with stubs once the auto-generated
自动生成的带有存根的jar
tests pass you have to put it into your
测试通过，您必须将其放入您的
CI pipeline the consumer uses stub
消费者使用的CI管道存根
rather to download the stops from Nexus
而不是从Nexus下载停靠站
this is exactly the same way as you have
这与您完全一样
seen during the demo summary so what did
在演示摘要中看到了，所以做了什么
we achieve with sprinkle contract and
我们通过洒水合同来实现
consumer-driven contract so we've
消费者驱动的合同，所以我们
created an API that suits the consumer
创建了适合消费者的API
and the producer like both sides are
双方的生产者都是
happy expectations were defined by
幸福的期望是由
readable contracts which means the DBA
可读合同，这意味着DBA
is can read those files and those those
是可以读取那些文件和那些
contracts also you have that description
合同你也有那个描述
field there when you can provide
可以在那里提供
arbitrary text expectations were tested
测试了任意文本期望
against the producer so if the contract
对生产者不利，因此如果合同
if the producer is lying in the contract
如果生产者在合同中
or is not meeting the contract it will
还是不履行合同，它将
not build itself so the stubs will not
没有建立自己，所以存根不会
be uploaded so nobody will be able to
被上传，所以没有人能够
reuse it you have to tell the truth and
重用它，你必须说出真相，
since we are uploading the stubs into
因为我们正在将存根上传到
Nexus or artifactory
Nexus或人工制品
everybody can be used in starting and
每个人都可以用来启动和
setting up stubs is fully automated as
设置存根是完全自动化的
you can see like you put an annotation
您可以看到就像您添加注释一样
things happen like automatically so why
事情像自动发生一样，为什么
could you sprinkle contracts verifier so
你能撒合同验证者吗
the bigger project verifier is the
更大的项目验证者是
plugin the stub runner all of that is
插入存根运行器所有这一切是
underneath the project goes to the spec
该项目下的规格
of contract verified you can do CDC of
合同证明您可以进行CDC
symmetric contracts also with messaging
对称合同也带有消息传递
not only HTTP requests so we can define
不仅是HTTP请求，所以我们可以定义
that such an input message can come and
这样的输入消息可以来了
such an out message will be sent and
这样的出去消息将被发送，
we're checking that against the producer
我们正在与生产者核对
as well it has clear and easy to use
以及清晰易用
statically typed DSL and automatically
静态类型的DSL并自动
geo tests are generated from that
地理测试由此产生
contract which is really important stop
合同真的很重要
runner automatically download stubs at
赛跑者自动在以下位置下载存根
runtime so you Tenuta have to think
运行时，所以您Tenuta必须考虑
about it happens out of the
关于它发生在
we integrate with sprinkler so if you
我们与洒水器集成在一起，因此，如果您
have discovery service you're using
有您正在使用的发现服务
console for example and you cannot do an
例如控制台，您将无法执行
in memory console you can use sprinkle
在内存控制台中，您可以使用洒
contract stub rather because it will
合同存根而不是因为它将
stop out the service discovery
停止服务发现
automatically so it will route to a
自动将其路由到
proper wiremock instance for you and we
适合您和我们的Wiremock实例
have an integration with cloud foundry
与Cloud Foundry集成
so there is a project called stub runner
所以有一个叫存根的项目
boot so you can run an application stub
启动，以便您可以运行应用程序存根
runner boot tell it to download certain
转轮启动告诉它下载某些
stubs and you can even tells the browser
存根，甚至可以告诉浏览器
to please register them in Eureka or
请在尤里卡注册或
please reviews a real rabbit and queue
请评论一只真正的兔子并排队
if you want to send trigger some
如果你想发送触发一些
messages from contract you can check
您可以查看合同中的消息
sprinkles pipelines project where
洒管道项目在哪里
incorporated there and you can check it
在那里合并，您可以检查一下
out how it works ok so that was it from
知道它是如何工作的，那是来自
my side so that will be time for
我的身边，这将是时候
questions from your side and yeah so
从你这边问的是的
just like whenever you have some doubts
就像每当您有疑问时
just read the dogs you can check out the
只是读狗，你可以签出
samples because we have in sprinkle
样本，因为我们在撒
contract special standalone samples
合同特殊独立样品
which are real applications that can
这是可以
talk to each other in our using skin
在我们使用皮肤时互相交谈
care contract and there is also the
护理合同，还有
getter channel where we'll be more than
吸气剂渠道，我们将超越
happy to answer your questions
很高兴回答您的问题
awesome great hey thanks mercy nyan yes
很棒，很好，谢谢，恩慈，恩
umm there are a number of questions go
嗯，还有很多问题
ahead oh yeah yeah ok so actually there
哦，是的，所以实际上在那里
are a whole bunch so let's um let's not
是一大堆，所以我们嗯，不要
spend too much time in each individual
在每个人身上花费太多时间
one umm so hang on just a second sorry
一umm，请稍等片刻
about
关于
that um first question comes from
那个第一个问题来自
andreas our friend andreas Evers from
andreas我们的朋友andreas Evers来自
ordina on he said if I understand it
奥尔迪娜对他说，如果我理解
correctly you're using the producers
正确地，您使用生产者
repo and maven build to install the
回购和Maven构建以安装
contracts into the maven repo pact is
签订了Maven回购协议
doing this with a separate pact broker
与单独的契约经纪人一起做
which is an HTTP server that you can
这是您可以使用的HTTP服务器
post and get contracts to and from the
发布合同并与之签订合同
sake of decoupling wouldn't that
为了脱钩不是吗
approach make more sense in having a
这种方法更有意义
clone a Java repo run maven while your
在您克隆Java repo运行Maven时
consumer could be written in JavaScript
消费者可以用JavaScript编写
and you know let's pretend that you know
你知道，让我们假装你知道
you're maybe not familiar with Java
您可能不熟悉Java
maven or groovy is a very very good
Maven或groovy是非常非常好的
question yes that's makes a very good
问题是的，这非常好
sense
感
so yes I guess this question was asked
所以是的，我想这个问题被问到了
before I shown this central repo so it
在我展示这个中央仓库之前
partly it's answered so it all depends I
部分地回答了这一切都取决于我
think so sorry was that you can explain
觉得很抱歉，您可以解释一下
right but only to some exceed it answers
对，但只有一些超出它的答案
only to some expense so the answer is
只是要花一些钱，所以答案是
that it's a matter of preference I
这是我的偏爱
personally prefer when the contracts lay
合同订立时个人更喜欢
with the producer but like I present it
与制作人一起，但就像我介绍的那样
it's not always possible so this is the
这并不总是可能的，所以这是
first thing another one is like I
第一件事是另一个像我
personally like the idea of the broker
个人喜欢经纪人的想法
and I like to act as such because pack
我喜欢这样，因为包
gives you the possibility to let's say
让您可以说
use consumer driven contracts with
使用与消费者驱动的合同
different languages so here we have we
不同的语言，所以我们在这里
are kind of bound to JVM and there was
是某种绑定到JVM，并且
like precisely the idea from the very
恰恰是从
beginning because this is part of the
开始，因为这是
umbrella project of splinter culture but
碎片文化的保护伞项目
we are planning to increase the
我们正计划增加
integration with pact we are planning to
与我们计划达成的协议
allow you to define the contracts using
允许您使用定义合同
pact files and also in my twisted mind I
契约文件，而且在我扭曲的头脑中，我
had an idea where as a broker could work
有一个经纪人可以在哪里工作的想法
with the Sprint Cup contract dear Souls
与Sprint杯合同亲爱的灵魂
as well so like to recap it's a matter
也想回顾一下这是一个问题
of preference
偏好
and right now if you have a lot of
现在，如果您有很多
different languages roaming around a
不同语言漫游
pact will most likely work more in a
公约将更有可能在
better automated way you can also
更好的自动化方式
achieve similar things with spell
用咒语达到类似的目的
contract already because you can use
已经签约，因为您可以使用
stop runner boots to run the stubs of
停止跑步者跑鞋的存根
like if you have an angular app for
例如，如果您有用于
example nodejs hub and it's
示例nodejs中心，它是
communicating with with a Java app for
与Java应用通信
instance then you can run the stub
实例，那么您可以运行存根
runner boots and tell it to download the
跑步靴，并告诉它下载
stubs that the node.js app needs and
node.js应用程序需要的存根和
that's it so you will have again the
就是这样，您将再次拥有
fake HTTP servers run and the node.js
伪造的HTTP服务器运行并且node.js
app will be able to communicate with
应用将能够与之通信
these stuff actually this was what
这些东西实际上就是
happened in one of my former company
发生在我以前的公司之一
that the UI was written with react and
用户界面是用react和
the guys were using the stub Runner
伙计们正在使用存根转轮
boots so to say options exactly the way
可以这么说
I asked presented in their build
我问他们提出了
pipeline they had it incorporated in
他们将其纳入的管道
their build pipeline actually thank you
他们的构建管道实际上谢谢你
very much yeah um that makes that makes
是的，嗯，这使得
sense and I think our next question is
感觉，我认为我们的下一个问题是
hopefully I think this one's pretty
希望我觉得这很漂亮
short um can I have multi-level
简短，我可以多层次吗
contracts defined to mock the
定义为模拟合同
integration tests multi levels from oh
集成测试从多个级别开始
yeah I'm loving loving I don't exactly
是的，我爱我不完全
understand what multi level contracts
了解什么多层次合同
mean but if somebody is referring to
意思是，但如果有人指的是
things like stateful situations like
有状态的情况
scenarios for example then yes you may
例如场景，那么你可以
have them we do support scenarios but I
有他们，我们确实支持方案，但我
would discourage using scenarios because
会阻止使用方案，因为
we do not want to replicate our features
我们不想复制我们的功能
right so what does it mean let's say
对，那是什么意思
that coming back to this beer fraud
回到啤酒欺诈中
check case right so if let's say that we
检查大小写正确，所以如果我们说
have 500 different ways of saying the
有500种不同的说法
person
人
Jaromir yeah Marcia mercy sorry uh he's
Jaromir是的Marcia怜悯抱歉，他是
um he's clarifying and he says if I have
嗯，他正在澄清，他说如果我有
a series of multi-level service calls a
一系列的多级服务称为
lot of multi-levels not really so let's
并不是很多，所以让我们
say series of can the person like
说一个人可以喜欢的系列
explain what like multi-level call yeah
解释多层次呼叫是什么
I can define any sort of requests and
我可以定义任何类型的请求，
really means like as you wish right yeah
真的就像您希望的那样
I will he is clarifying further and
我将他进一步澄清，
saying service a sort calling service PT
称服务为分类呼叫服务PT
which is calling service fee I think oh
我想这是电话服务费哦
no no absolutely not absolutely not that
不不绝对不是绝对不是
I mean that's the very idea that we
我的意思是，我们
don't want so we want to test in
不想，所以我们想测试一下
isolation so basically if you go to
隔离，所以基本上如果你去
drink out the pipeline's project to the
喝完管道的项目
documentation I explicitly write there
我在那里明确写的文档
like the very idea behind the let's say
就像让我们说的背后的想法
those Stubbings so let's say we want to
这些存根，所以我们要
factor feedback so first thing is I want
因素反馈，所以我首先要
to test my app in isolation I build it
孤立地测试我的应用程序
so I'm going calling service B I don't
所以我要打电话给BI
care about service see I don't even know
关心服务，我什至不知道
that it exists I don't care that because
它存在，我不在乎，因为
C right so I as a as a as a consumer of
C对，所以我作为一个消费者
that service B I will like write only
该服务BI只会写
contracts that are I'm interested with
我感兴趣的合同
right I wouldn't use this like
对，我不会这样使用
completely I don't know mock out the
完全我不知道模拟了
like those who multi-level scenarios of
像那些多层次情景的人
course you can have stub for like be
当然你可以像
calling CC calling deeds that that makes
呼叫CC呼叫行为
perfect sense right because you need
完美的感觉对，因为你需要
some you need those contracts but I
有些你需要那些合同，但是我
cannot imagine like having some more
无法想象还有更多
complex like stops the idea here is also
像停止复杂的想法在这里也是
that if you and I would encourage
如果你和我会鼓励
everybody checks pick up the pipeline is
大家检查接管
over there if you have good alerting
如果你有很好的警报，那边
good metrics good KPI monitoring then
好的指标，然后进行良好的KPI监控
you can actually get rid of end-to-end
您实际上可以摆脱端到端的局面
tests why because we
测试为什么，因为我们
check everything with contract so we are
检查所有与合同，所以我们
sure that the semantics is okay that on
确保语义是可以的
production you will never you shouldn't
生产，你永远不会，你不应该
have a problem with like that the
有这样的问题
request is mouth forms or something like
请求是嘴形或类似
that it doesn't mean of course that the
那当然并不意味着
feature is working but if you have a
功能正在运作，但如果您有
very fast pipeline you can immediately
非常快速的管道，您可以立即
roll back to a previous version right so
回滚到以前的版本吧
that way maybe this answers the question
这样也许可以回答问题
to some extent is that you can if you're
在某种程度上是可以的
doing those contract tests and you have
做那些合同测试，你有
fast feedback and you can go faster
快速的反馈，您可以更快
production and roll back to a previous
生产并回滚到上一个
version you can get rid of end-to-end
您可以摆脱端到端版本的版本
tests you can do it them locally like to
测试您可以在本地进行，例如
be sure I would do it as a developer but
确保我会以开发人员的身份来做，但是
you can get rid of them uh in the big
你可以在大范围内摆脱它们
pipeline great okay thank you thank you
管道很好，谢谢，谢谢
um OOP let's see uh I'm trying to keep
哎呀，让我们看看我正在努力保持
up with question queue here wolf there's
与问题队列在一起，这里有狼
there's la come in on Lucca asks um
卢卡进来的人问
let's say that the producer is my client
假设制作人是我的客户
and I don't have any rights to clone
而且我没有克隆任何权利
that Rico then how can I manage it so we
那Rico那我该如何管理它，所以我们
can have a common repo as like they
可以像他们一样有一个通用的仓库
presented so we can like if that is a
介绍，所以我们可以喜欢，如果这是一个
client then ah like we have two options
客户然后啊，就像我们有两个选择
either they cooperate and we create some
他们要么合作，我们创造一些
private github repo where they have
他们在那里的私人github回购
access and both sides agree on some
访问和双方都同意一些
stuff or if that's not possible I would
的东西，或者如果那不可能，我会
ask them to provide a test environment
要求他们提供测试环境
with their tests like App III could
像App III这样的测试可以
write some contracts but they're pretty
写一些合同，但它们很漂亮
useless if I I cannot you know let's say
如果我不知道我说的话没用
exercise them against the clients like
像客户一样对他们进行锻炼
like I mean that's the like power of
就像我的意思是
this tool is that I checking if the
这个工具是我检查
contract is telling the truth if the
合同说的是实话
consumer is my client and they don't
消费者是我的客户，但他们不是
want to cooperate they don't use the
想要合作，他们不使用
tool then we have a problem and what I
工具，那么我们有一个问题，我
would like I mean I would expect them to
我想我希望他们能
give me an environment where they have
给我一个他们拥有的环境
some sort of a test app that I can call
我可以调用的某种测试应用
real request that's what I would
真正的要求就是我要的
personally do that makes sense anything
个人认为这有意义
that feels really realistic to you right
对你来说真的很现实
you know because sometimes these these
你知道，因为有时候这些
web services you know they might they
您知道他们可能会使用的Web服务
might be outside the four walls your
可能在四壁之外
business um that makes a lot of sense
非常有意义的业务
tool thank you um Enrique asks hi I
工具谢谢恩里克问你好我
would like to know how you would run the
想知道您将如何运行
producer tests when the producer itself
当生产者本身时，生产者进行测试
is a consumer of some other service and
是其他服务的消费者，并且
you don't want to have that dependency
你不想有这种依赖
as part of your tests I don't have all
作为测试的一部分，我没有全部
the yeah I mean so maybe I will say it
是的，我的意思是，也许我会说
again so I as a producer I'm calling
再次，我作为制作人打电话
somebody else right okay so uh that's a
有人吧，好吧，那是一个
very very good question so let me go
非常非常好的问题，让我走
back if I I don't know if everybody can
如果我不知道每个人都可以
see me like the code will be maybe
看到我喜欢的代码可能是
showing that and talking at the same
表现出来并同时说话
time so basically if you have a
时间，基本上，如果你有一个
controller on the producer side so we
生产者方面的控制器，所以我们
have those auto-generated tests they are
有那些自动生成的测试
calling sending real requests so here
打电话发送真实的请求，所以在这里
for the sake of demo I did a
为了演示，我做了一个
simplification to put it like to say the
简化地说
least so over here I've created the I
至少在这里，我创建了I
wrote the real implementation by the way
顺便写了真正的实现
Peter can everybody see the screen right
彼得可以让所有人看到正确的屏幕
yes sure I'll have you there confident I
是的，我一定会让你有信心
just didn't want to interrupt you I had
只是不想打扰我
no problem so what I should do is that I
没问题，所以我应该做的是
should do for example an interface
应该做一个接口
called producer fee service and with a
称为生产者收费服务，并带有
methods like respawns
诸如重生之类的方法
of course it shouldn't look like this
当然不应该是这样
it's like I'm doing this fast so check
就像我正在快速地做，所以检查
if eligible eligible check is okay I
如果合格的合格支票还可以，我
don't know maybe I misspelled it so and
不知道也许我拼错了
we do person to check here so what
我们有人在这里检查，所以
should happen is actually that we oughta
应该发生的实际上是我们应该
wire a
连线
service here producer service Oh we do
服务在这里生产者服务哦，我们愿意
it like this we do return producer
像这样我们会退还生产者
service check if ok and we mark this
服务检查是否还可以，我们对此进行了标记
thing that we do not run the real logic
我们不运行真正逻辑的事情
so if if underneath I am calling some
所以如果在下面我打电话给
real stuff I don't want to be doing that
真正的东西我不想那样做
because I don't want to check the
因为我不想检查
implementation I want to check only the
实现我只想检查
semantics so how do I do that
语义，那么我该怎么做
in the poem you define the base glass
在这首诗中，您定义了玻璃杯
for tests either it can be one or you
用于测试可以是一个或您
can define a series of them or there is
可以定义其中的一系列，或者有
a convention so inside the base class
在基类内部的约定
which I have over here I'm doing a
我在这里做的是
standalone set up for put my controller
独立设置用于放置控制器
actually Oliver view I would kill me for
其实奥利弗认为我会杀了我
doing this like this so let me do it
这样做，让我做
properly with a constructor uh yeah
与构造函数正确地相处
actually three like this so over here
其实三个像这样
right now in the base class I need the
现在在基类中，我需要
producer service so what I would do is
生产者服务，所以我要做的是
let me do a poor-man's version fast I'm
让我快做一个穷人的版本
doing a producer service producer
做一个生产者服务的生产者
service mockito mock of a producer
生产者的服务模拟
service and here I have to do all the
服务，在这里我必须做所有
Givens and winds and then so for example
吉风和风，然后例如
mockito
模仿
given i don't have VD D so when producer
鉴于我没有VD D，所以当制作人时
service is cold I'm going to do some
服务很冷我要去做一些
pseudo code here right so a person to
伪代码在这里，这样一个人
check with proper age then return for
检查适当的年龄然后返回
example response would be new response
示例响应将是新响应
with beer check status ok something like
啤酒检查状态还可以
this right and with improper age then
这项权利和不适当的年龄
the beer check status would be not ok so
啤酒检查状态不好
assuming that I would be calling some
假设我会打电话给一些
database underneath or something like
下面的数据库或类似的东西
that I don't want to do it I don't want
我不想做我不想
to integrate with anybody else it's a
与其他人融合是一个
mock that should be present here in the
模拟应该在这里出现
producer
生产者
so like directly here no real
所以就像直接在这里没有真实
interaction should take place I mean
互动应该发生
this is my personal opinion and it has
这是我个人的看法，
some valid grounds but I know companies
一些有效的理由，但我知道公司
that don't do it like this and they use
不这样做，他们使用
contracts to do some even end-to-end
签订一些端到端的合同
tests but these are really like specific
测试，但是这些真的很具体
cases what I would suggest is that you
我建议的情况是你
do not replicate functionality in the
不要在
contract and you do not make real calls
签订合同，您不进行真正的跟注
underneath to a database or another
在数据库或其他数据库的下面
service got it okay thanks for that that
服务还可以，谢谢
that's that's a really important
那是非常重要的
clarification on the Semitic source the
澄清闪族的来源
implementation thank you um okay and
实施谢谢你好吧，
let's see I guess we got that one from
让我们看看我猜是从
Enrique let's see um Roy Roy limit is n
Enrique让我们看一下Roy Roy的极限是n
I yeah Roy esra or roll excuse me
我是罗伊·埃斯拉或劳拉
start from your name they're on
从你的名字开始
sometimes the service that I integrate
有时我整合的服务
with its serving data for example excuse
以其投放数据为例
serving data for example sometimes I
例如有时提供数据
need to have tests that simulate
需要进行模拟测试
different data sets from the producer
生产者提供的不同数据集
for the test on the consumer how can
对于消费者的测试如何
this be achieved think sometimes I need
做到这一点，有时我需要
to have different sets of data right so
拥有不同的数据集
okay so but I mean for the same URL
好的，但是我的意思是相同的网址
right so basically with DES I was fake
对，所以基本上用DES我是假的
right yeah I would think yeah exactly
是的，我想是的
simulate so you can have a different
模拟，以便您可以拥有不同的
sponsor for the tests on the consumer so
赞助消费者的测试，所以
let's say you define poor like let's go
假设您定义穷人就像我们走
to this beer situation so let's say that
面对这种啤酒情况，我们可以说
you for some reason and it makes sense
您出于某种原因，这很有意义
for you because you know the more
为你，因为你知道更多
contracts you have the more it becomes a
合约越多，它就变成了
support burden right the most has to be
最应该支持的负担
okay
好的
like for the producer it might become a
对于生产者来说，它可能会变成
problem if you have billions of of
问题，如果你有数十亿
scenarios to support because you need to
支持方案，因为您需要
create those mocks underneath so if
在下面创建那些模拟
let's say it may
可以说
sense you can create four different
感觉你可以创造四个不同
let's say different requests return
假设有不同的要求返回
different response so what we did in one
不同的响应，所以我们在一处做了
of my previous companies is we for
我以前的公司是我们
example created different because we had
这个例子创造了不同，因为我们有
a scenario where somebody could be a
一个人可能是一个场景
fraud and and you can be a fraud for a
欺诈，而您可能会欺诈
number of reasons let's say I know five
数量原因，假设我知道五个
hundred different options so for being a
一百种不同的选择
fraud so we picked five most important
欺诈，所以我们选了五个最重要的
and for example we differentiated them
例如我们将它们区分开
by name for example if the client's name
按名称（例如，客户名称）
is I don't know throws one then you
是我不知道会丢一个然后你
return concrete stages or something like
返回具体阶段或类似的东西
that so I mean this is this is test data
所以我的意思是这是测试数据
right so then on the consumer side if we
对，那么在消费者方面，如果我们
need it like we could have picked one of
需要它，就像我们本可以选择其中一个
those five scenarios depending on the
这五个场景取决于
things you need to test but like let me
您需要测试但要让我做的事情
emphasize it again it's it if you can be
再强调一次，如果可以的话
a fraud for three hundred different
三百种不同的欺诈
reasons I would wouldn't assume that
我不会假设的原因
you're gonna have free hunt contract I
你将有免费狩猎合同我
would assume you would have to so you
会假设你必须这样做
are a fraud or not why because if you
是不是欺诈？为什么，如果你
have a proper onion layer architecture
具有适当的洋葱层架构
so then on a consumer side those
所以在消费者方面
consumer tests would be like only on
消费者测试就像
some tiny layer to see if we can
一些微小的层，看看我们是否可以
communicate properly the real like tests
正确沟通真实的测试
in terms of like okay
就好吧
you can be a fraud because of this you
你可能因此而成为欺诈
can see folder because of that I would
可以看到文件夹，因为我会
like mug a mock out the this call right
像马克杯这样的模拟电话
to to a to the producer why because I
到制作人的原因，因为我
can have faster feedback because I will
可以得到更快的反馈，因为我会
note the real integration tests I will
注意我将进行的真正的集成测试
not do real calls and I I can I can do
我不可以打电话，我可以做
it fast so basically you should have a
它很快，所以基本上你应该有一个
lot of like unit tests not that many
很多类似的单元测试不是很多
integration tests a part of which can be
集成测试的一部分可以是
get the contract test right I would
得到合同测试的权利，我会
really use them to to check if we can
真的用它们来检查我们是否可以
talk properly instead of checking if the
说话正确，而不是检查
features are working fine great
功能正常工作很棒
okay we're almost we're doing pretty
好吧，我们差不多要做的很漂亮
good more scenery we're getting there um
好多的风景，我们到那里
there's only a couple left um okay let's
剩下几对了，好吧，让我们
see um well I think you kind of answered
很好，我想你已经回答了
this already actually I'll look uh uh
这实际上我会看起来
who was asking a question earlier about
谁在提早一个问题
multi level you know chain contracts is
您知道连锁合同的多层次
asking a question about you know what
问一个关于你的问题知道什么
happens if I'm a Java developer or the
如果我是Java开发人员或
consumers are they two different
消费者是他们两个不同
language like Java Script how can you
Java Script之类的语言
use these contrasts you know a tests
使用这些对比，您就会知道测试
written in Spock um okay yeah very good
用Spock写的，嗯，是的，很好
so maybe we can pursue some explain only
所以也许我们只能进行一些解释
I will I will only like give it fast so
我会只想快点给
basically this is what I'm wearing I
基本上这就是我穿的衣服
can't believe that the JavaScript
不能相信JavaScript
developer will not be able to install
开发人员将无法安装
Nathan so if you have a Linux box you do
内森（Nathan），如果您有Linux电脑
sudo apt-get install Nathan and then you
sudo apt-get安装Nathan，然后您
just write maven clean install - this
只需编写Maven全新安装-这个
kit tests that's it right it was that
套件测试是正确的
way you will install the stubs locally
您将在本地安装存根的方式
that is so I really do not believe that
所以我真的不相信
it can be a problem for somebody like if
对于某些人来说可能是个问题
somebody can run npm install or
有人可以运行npm install或
something like that the person can write
那个人可以写的东西
maven again like maven dot like clean
Maven再次像Maven点一样干净
install the skip test
安装跳过测试
it's very trivial it's documented I
这很琐碎
cannot believe that it can be a problem
不敢相信这可能是一个问题
for somebody fair enough yeah it does
对于一个足够公平的人，是的
sound pretty straightforward um okay and
听起来很简单，嗯，
then I'm Andrew Morgan from open creo
那我是开放Creo的Andrew Morgan
asks because you auto generate or infer
询问是因为您自动生成或推断
contracts by interacting with API that
通过与API交互来签订合同
already exists oh and that's that's a
已经存在哦，那就是
nice one so we were thinking about this
不错的一个，所以我们正在考虑这个
but you can have it will not be trivial
但你可以拥有它不会是微不足道的
why because for example when you're
为什么，因为例如当你
using spring data you know the API is
使用spring数据，您知道API是
automatically created so to say the
自动创建，可以这么说
controller so that wouldn't be that easy
控制器，所以不会那么容易
and actually you don't want to stop
实际上你不想停下来
everything so you know it's like it's
一切，所以你知道这就像
kind of problematic but
有点问题，但
you're thinking about doing this the
您正在考虑这样做
other way around how about creating a
另一种方法是如何创建一个
controller from the contract and that's
合同的控制者，那就是
the thing we have in our backlog so
我们积压的东西，所以
imagine this but the consumers are
想象一下，但是消费者
creating a new API like completely new
创建一个像全新的新API
on new URL something like that
在新的网址上像这样
and then the producer once it takes over
然后生产者接管
the PR like automatically does something
公关喜欢自动做某事
and this print out contract plugin would
这个打印输出合同插件会
generate the controller that matches
生成匹配的控制器
that contract with fake data for example
例如，带有虚假数据的合同
the ones that you provide in the
您在其中提供的
contract that would be awesome
很棒的合同
and we're thinking about this very cool
我们正在考虑这很酷
on oh my gosh I can't believe it we're
哦，天哪，我简直不敢相信我们
getting close to the end here um okay uh
快结束了，嗯，嗯，嗯
I'm going to say his name wrong um so
我要说他的名字错了，所以
maybe I shouldn't try but it's something
也许我不应该尝试，但这是
like Disney tree um from bear ask when
就像迪斯尼的熊从树上问
the tests run on the producer side does
在生产方运行的测试确实
the contract test actually call the
合同测试实际上称为
intended end points for example testing
预期的终点，例如测试
a post endpoint would create an entity
后端点将创建一个实体
in producer DB every time now I think
我现在每次都在生产者数据库中
the answer this is no right um is your
答案不对，嗯，是你的
calling the mock yes exactly yes yeah
叫模拟是完全正确是的
yeah okay okay right I just wanted to be
是的，好的，好的，我只是想成为
sure
当然
well precisely everything you wouldn't
恰恰是您所不愿的一切
call the because you wouldn't past past
致电，因为您不会过去
the controller because you're talking to
控制器，因为您正在与
a mock I'm just writing that in the
我只是在写一个模拟
console forum here hang on okay okay all
控制台论坛在这里挂好所有好
right
对
ah very good very good okay excellent
啊很好很好很好很好
um hmm um okay so you're you're you're
嗯嗯嗯好吧，你就是你，你就是
um from a company name that I'm going to
嗯，我要去的公司名称是
slaughter the pronunciation of asks in
屠杀ask的发音
our example we had a single consumer
在我们的示例中，我们只有一个消费者
with a client contract and a producer
与客户合同和生产者
with a server contract uh but could our
与服务器合同呃，但我们可以
producer have a consumer contract with
生产者与
another producer at the same time let me
同时有另一位制片人
know if you want me to read that again
知道你是否要我再读一遍
because I got a little confused you
因为我有点困惑你
please
请
okay okay all right
好吧好吧好吧
basically he's saying do you know that
基本上他是在说你知道吗
we know that I know that unit notice
我们知道我知道该单位的通知
getting um in our example we had a
在我们的示例中，我们有一个
single consumer with a quiet contract
签约安静的单一消费者
and a producer with a server contract
和具有服务器合同的生产者
sorry I mean well I have a consumer with
对不起，我是说我有一个消费者
a client conference right
客户会议权
I mean they say an hour is a medic it is
我是说他们说一个小时是医生
okay it is exhibit that's not yours not
好吧，那不是你的展览
yours
你的
what is example um so once again in his
嗯，是什么例子
example let's say he had a single
举例说他有一个
consumer with a client contract and a
具有客户合同和
producer with a server contract ah but
生产者与服务器签订合同啊但是
could our producer have a consumer
我们的生产者能有一个消费者吗
contract with another producer at the
与另一家生产商签订合同
same time I don't know if that's it's
同时我不知道那是不是
kind of hard to follow but I mean I am
有点难以遵循，但我是说我
say I don't need any constitute of
说我不需要任何构成
client contracts I would say it's an
客户合同我会说这是一个
expectation right so okay I think I get
期望正确，好吧，我想我明白了
it
它
so so basically that would be the case
所以基本上就是这样
where if you're a common repo like when
如果您是常见的仓库，例如
you have a common repo with all the
您与所有
contracts you can call those contracts
合约你可以称之为合约
expectations why because the consumers
期望为什么因为消费者
are putting under the folder of the
放在下面的文件夹
person specific producer how they would
个人特定的制作人
like the producer to behave so let's say
像制片人那样表现，所以说
that we have a group ID ABC and the
我们有一个组ID ABC和
archive artifact ID will be producer
存档工件ID将是生产者
right and then we have three consumers
对，然后我们有三个消费者
of that producer so in the common
那个生产者的共同点
repository with all the contracts you
包含您所有合同的资料库
would have a folder a / b /c / producer
会有一个文件夹a / b / c / producer
under which we would have three folders
在此之下，我们将拥有三个文件夹
consumer one consumer two and consumer
消费者一消费者二和消费者
free so all of those consumers would
免费，所以所有这些消费者都会
place their expectations on how the API
对API寄予期望
should look like but this will be one
应该看起来像，但这将是一个
thing right so then the producer would
没事，那么制片人会
like the test would be generated for for
就像测试将针对
him from this repo but you could also
他来自这个仓库，但你也可以
have that producer has its own like
让那个制作人有自己的风格
contracts on his side so you can have
在他身边签约，这样你就可以
like a two phase comments to say so you
像两个阶段的评论这样说
have the contract duplicated
重复合同
like if you need the bigger safety but I
就像您需要更大的安全性，但我
had I think it's like like too much so
我是否觉得这太过分了
so you should pick one of those one of
所以你应该选择其中之一
those approaches and I don't know if I
这些方法，我不知道我是否
properly understood the question so I'm
正确理解了这个问题，所以我
shutting up I'm not sure if I did either
闭嘴我不确定我是否做过
to be honest because he just clarified
说实话，因为他只是澄清了
and said with the client I just met your
跟客户说我刚遇到你
consumer examples so yargh
如此庞大的消费者案例
I think maybe this isn't it this is an
我想也许这不是，这是一个
instance where you guys might want to
你们可能想要的实例
collaborate on Gator this this point yes
在这方面与Gator合作
really isn't best um for first trying to
真的不是第一次尝试的最佳选择
get this one out feels like a diagram is
得到这个感觉就像一张图
a good idea sorry about that
一个好主意，对此感到抱歉
um and believe it or not I think we've
嗯，信不信由你，我想我们已经
run to the end of the question queue
运行到问题队列的末尾
folks this is a good time to look at
乡亲，这是一个看的好时机
your on 24 interface and go down to the
您在24界面上，然后转到
resources tab uh and then excuse me and
“资源”标签，然后对不起，
then there is some there are some links
然后有一些有一些链接
there with some follow-up information
那里有一些后续信息
that that you can kind of get a hold of
这样你就可以掌握
pretty easily on a number of things like
很容易在很多事情上
you know the blog entry about the
您知道有关
release there's an article from Martin
发布，有一篇马丁的文章
Fowler on consumer driven contracts
福勒以消费者为导向的合同
there's a link to the github repo and a
有一个链接到github repo和一个
bunch of other really good stuff great
一堆其他真的很好的东西很棒
um and Marcin I didn't have a chance to
嗯，马辛，我没有机会
check out check this out but I think
查看此内容，但我认为
it's a mate this is a maven download
这是一个伴侣，这是一个行家下载
right so if people want to get their
对，所以如果人们想得到他们的
hands on actual bits this is just a
动手实际位，这只是一个
matter of plugging in some coordinates
插入一些坐标的问题
- maybe in central yeah so oh yeah so
-也许在中央
basic basically you're asking about the
基本来说，你是在问
the library is such right so it's more
图书馆是正确的所以更多
complex right because there is a bunch
复杂的权利，因为有一堆
of missing they're like moving pieces
思念他们就像在移动碎片
there so I would suggest going to the
在那里，所以我建议去
contract page to string our contract
合同页面以签订合同
page and checking out the introduction
页并查看介绍
and in the main page you can see like
在主页上您可以看到
all the dependencies needed by the
所有需要的依赖
producer and Vanessa's by a consumer we
制片人和凡妮莎的消费者我们
do a step by step guide for this so I
为此做一步一步的指导，所以我
would just go into the project page
只会进入项目页面
checking it out from there like what
从那里检查出来像什么
what is exactly needed okay okay got it
到底需要什么好吧好吧
so this might be a more of an instance
所以这可能更多是一个实例
of let's clone the repo as opposed to
让我们克隆回购而不是
let's plug in some maven coordinates
让我们插入一些Maven坐标
okay um
好的，嗯
very good alrighty and then I think
很好，然后我认为
that's about it if you are um oh yeah if
就是这样，如果你是哦，是的，如果
you're curious about what the next
你很好奇下一个
webinar we're going to be but doing is
我们将要举行的网络研讨会，但要做的是
we're continuing in kind of our micro
我们正在继续我们的微观
service beam and distributed system
服务波束和分布式系统
scheme with Josh long and a large from
乔什（Josh）的计划
try Fork
尝试叉
who is the one domain committers behind
谁是背后的域名提交者
the axon CQRS framework and that's going
轴突CQRS框架
to be on Wednesday November 16th
将于11月16日（星期三）
um if you would like to join us for that
嗯，如果你想加入我们
webinar um you can there's a link to it
网络研讨会，您可以找到一个链接
in the question and answer panel of the
在“问题和答案”面板中
on 24 interface or you can also just go
在24界面上，或者您也可以
to spring dot IO /blog on and you'll see
启动IO / blog，您会看到
a post you just scroll down a teeny bit
帖子，您只需向下滚动即可
and you'll see it post about the webinar
然后您会看到有关网络研讨会的帖子
it's on November 16
在11月16日
um so please feel free to join us for
嗯，请随时加入我们
that and invite your colleagues um and
然后邀请你的同事
then like I said registered um please
然后像我说的注册嗯
register or subscribe to the blog or the
注册或订阅博客或
YouTube channel so you get a
YouTube频道，因此您可以
notification of the the replay the
重播的通知
slides being available and I'm Marcin
幻灯片可用，我是Marcin
there's a number of people just sync
有很多人只是同步
thank you um and I'm thinking uh you
谢谢你，我在想你
know offering offering you some great
知道提供给您一些很棒的东西
job feedback and um one person saying uh
工作反馈和一个人说呃
hearing you is so much better than
听到你比说要好得多
reading you check those cute oh yeah so
看你检查那些可爱的哦，是的，所以
maybe I have to finish my writing so
也许我必须完成我的写作，所以
anything else you want to say before we
您想在我们面前说什么
call it a day um thank you very much
每天都这样吧，非常感谢
I'm really happy that we could have this
我很高兴能有这个
discussion these conversations I really
讨论这些对话，我真的
loved to hear you like your feedback
很高兴听到您喜欢您的反馈
because only if you give us feedback we
因为只有您给我们反馈
can like make our tools better and we do
可以使我们的工具变得更好，我们可以
them for you so without you guys I mean
他们为你，所以没有你们我的意思是
our job is useless so please provide
我们的工作没有用，所以请提供
feedback the topic of sprinkles like the
反馈像洒的主题
consumer is given contracts and
消费者被授予合同，
contracts are
合同是
it's very like it's kind of old because
这很旧，因为
more than ten years since the if I
自从我走了十多年
remember correctly since the blog post
记住正确的自博客文章
from from I am but it is kind of complex
来自我，但这有点复杂
you can make school the consumer will
你可以让学校成为消费者
the producer but hopefully I've managed
制片人，但希望我能做到
to explain that like at least to clarify
至少要解释一下
some things and show what are the
一些东西，并显示什么是
benefits right that we're not talking
好处是我们不说话
about with those three zero like or
大约与这三个零类似或
something like that that is something
像那样的东西
completely different and it's solving
完全不同，它正在解决
real problems
实际问题
so hopefully have managed to show that
所以希望能够证明
have a great to everyone thanks and see
对每个人都有一个伟大的感谢和看到
you in the weather against you take care
在不利于您的天气中，您要小心
thanks
谢谢